yangutu.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy | Meetville | Meet the Right Person, Best Dating Apps for iPhone, iPad, Android

**1\. Automatically Gathered Information**

We use your IP address and cookies. IP is the series of numbers associated with the network you come from. This information does not disclose your personal details!

We need it to maintain our Web site and collect geographical statistics of our visitors. Cookies are small text files that web sites place on your hard drive to identify you when you come back. The use of cookies is a common practice on the Internet. You can disable all cookies through your browser settings.  

**2\. Information We Ask You to Provide Us**  
To register on our site you can create free profile or use Meetville Facebook App. The information that is required is the same as for Facebook registration. We don’t post anything on your timeline, thus keeping your registration a secret.

To sign up you can use Meetville Mobile as well. The only contact information we ask you to provide us with is your e-mail address. We don’t send you any confirmation letters to your e-mail address and don’t send any notifications without your permission as well.

Moreover, any identifying information you give us by signing up from Facebook will be kept private. We never share this information with other companies without your permission. Whenever we ask you for information, we make it absolutely clear whether it is visible to other users or not.

All your interaction with other Meetville users as well as with the Meetville team is strictly confidential. It will never be used for purposes of research or advertising without your permission.

**3\. Your Account Privacy Settings**  
Meetville account privacy settings allow you to set up privacy on the number of your profile aspects:

  * You can manage your profile privacy by going to settings at the top right of the window and then clicking on the account and set up who can view your profile.
  * You can adjust your chat settings for convenient messaging.
  * You have the opportunity to choose what types of the Meetville notifications to receive by e-mail.

The instructions to unsubscribe from our mailings are located in the bottom of the messages we send. There you can also find the direct link to unsubscribe with a single click.  

**4\. Meetville and Facebook Security**  
We don’t ask you to provide us with any additional information when you become Meetville fans on our Facebook Meetville page beside the initial information that is required to register on Facebook. After pushing the “Like” button you confirm that you agree to get all the Meetville news posted on your Facebook timeline.  The visibility of your Facebook timeline is regulated by the Facebook privacy settings.

**5\. Security**  
Meetville.com has implemented appropriate security measures to protect any user from the loss, misuse and change of users’ information and personal data. Meetville takes reasonable security measures to guarantee the confidentiality of your personal information. Our technical experts work hard to ensure your secure use of our site.

Although we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of our website, no site or Internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot prevent any possible unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal data safe (including your password) and to log out of your account.

**6\. Your Rights**

You can review and edit your profile information at any time. Having registered on Meetville.com you are able to review and edit the following personal information:

  * Your contact email address (after contacting Meetville Support Team)
  * Your name (after contacting Meetville Support Team)
  * Your photographs
  * Your city, region, and country of residence
  * Your age and other personal characteristics
  * Your password

Please constantly update your personal data if they change. We strongly urge you to change your password from time to time to reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your profile information.

**7.    Financial Security**  
We do not record or store your credit card information. Your payment details are encrypted with a secure socket layer technology (SSL) to ensure your payment data protection and transmitted directly to our processing company for authorization.

Please, [contact](http://meetville.com/dating/feedback) our Support Team in case any financial security questions occur.

**8.     Meetville’s partners**

Applications of such Meetville’s partners as:

_Match Dating, Tagged Dating, Tinder Dating, Pulse, Hello, Hot Dating, Flirt Dating, OK Cupid Dating, Matchmaker, Fish Dating, Sexy People, Dating, Asian Dating, Black Dating, Latin Dating, Senior Dating, Cupid Dating, Meet Me, QQ Dating, Live Dating, Conduit Dating, Sex Dating, Sex Offender, Sex Chat, Amazon Dating, Go Dating, Dating Cafe, Tango Dating, Tinderbox, Tender, Tender Dating, Arab Dating_ have an access to Meetville’s databases. As members of these applications are added to the large database they can receive Meetville notifications through email service. All applications are under licenses, authorizations, Terms and Privacy rules granted by Meetville.

These Privacy Policy was last modified on June 12, 2013.
